question.com 2016-05-13

# Privacy Policy - Question.com

For the purposes of this privacy policy, the terms "we", "us", "our" and "Question.com" refer to the Question.com website. The terms "You" and "End-User" refer to You as a user of this Site.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. We use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site and to provide you with enhanced services (viewing history, account information). A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. If you reject cookies, you can still use our site, but your ability to use or access some areas of our site may be limited. 

You may choose to provide us with personal information, by sending e-mail with questions or comments or by filling out an online form and submitting it to us through our web site. We use this information to;

  * Gather the requested information. 
  * Respond to Your message. 
  * Follow-up as appropriate. 

Question.com does not create individual profiles with the information You provide. If information is collected, it will be used solely in connection with Question.com, or for such other purposes as are described at the point of collection. Question.com does not give, sell, or transfer any personal information to any third party for their promotional purposes. 

However, Your e-mail message, question, or comment may be forwarded to other Question.com employees, contractors or subcontractors, who may be better able to help You. Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, we do not share our e-mail with any other outside organizations. However, e-mail and on-line forms are not secure against interception and senders cannot expect guaranteed privacy. 

## Security

Question.com follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. We use SSL (Secure Socket Layer) technology to protect your sensitive information on our site. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send an email using our contact form.

## Forum/Bulletin Board

If you use any forum/bulletin board or chat room on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. Question.com also reserves the right to terminate the accounts of visitors who use these services in a manner inconsistent with our Terms of Use.

## Refer a Friend

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Question.com does not store this information. 

## Registration

In order to use some areas of this web site, you must first complete the registration form. During registration you are required to provide contact information such as your name, age, email address, preferred username, password and preferred subscriptions. We will only use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest. You also have the option to provide demographic information to us; we encourage you to submit this information so we can provide you a more personalized experience on our site. 

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may update or deactivate your information by signing into your account or by emailing our Customer Support or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed above.

## Third Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) Some of these companies use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Question.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any third-party advertising companies.

## "Opting out"

We provide you the opportunity to ’opt-out’ of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you set up an account but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference during signup. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletters, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter, by signing into your account or by emailing us.

## Legal Disclosure

Question.com reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

## Changes to the Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.

_Updated: Oct 21, 2009_
